[{"answer": "Right now", "docId": "the-insider_shooting.txt", "asentId": 3, "question": "Why did you take your stuff from the office", "qsentId": 2}, {"answer": "Why did you take your stuff from the office", "docId": "the-insider_shooting.txt", "asentId": 5, "question": " I don't understand", "qsentId": 4}, {"answer": " Did you say my friend", "docId": "the-insider_shooting.txt", "asentId": 7, "question": " \"60 Minute", "qsentId": 6}, {"answer": " Doesn't CBS have confidentiality agreements, Mr. my friend", "docId": "the-insider_shooting.txt", "asentId": 9, "question": "Did work", "qsentId": 8}, {"answer": "Between journalists and management, yes, I believe they do...but I don't take that seriously.  Where do you work", "docId": "the-insider_shooting.txt", "asentId": 11, "question": " Did work", "qsentId": 10}, {"answer": "Why am I gonna mention your name", "docId": "the-insider_shooting.txt", "asentId": 13, "question": "How the hell do I know about my friend", "qsentId": 12}, {"answer": "How did my friend", "docId": "the-insider_shooting.txt", "asentId": 15, "question": "It  after I talked to you.  I do not like coincidences", "qsentId": 14}, {"answer": "How the hell do I know about my friend", "docId": "the-insider_shooting.txt", "asentId": 17, "question": "And I don't like paranoid accusations! I'm a journalist.  Think.  Use your head. How do I operate as a journalist by screwing the people who could provide me with information  they provided me with it", "qsentId": 16}, {"answer": "And I don't like paranoid accusations! I'm a journalist.  Think.  Use your head. How do I operate as a journalist by screwing the people who could provide me with information  they provided me with it", "docId": "the-insider_shooting.txt", "asentId": 19, "question": "No.  I did not.  Big Tobacco is a big story.  And you got something important to say.  I can tell.  But, yes.  I did. I came all the way down here to tell yo", "qsentId": 18}, {"answer": " And, I'm unemployed.  So I have to protect my medical coverage.  ...so I left them a message this morning. Their expanded confidentiality agreement? I will sign it", "docId": "the-insider_shooting.txt", "asentId": 21, "question": "They should be", "qsentId": 20}, {"answer": "Next to your father", "docId": "the-insider_shooting.txt", "asentId": 23, "question": "Is that why you became a journalist? Then you get to ask all the questions", "qsentId": 22}, {"answer": "You should.  Because when you're done, a judgment is going to go down in the court of public opinion, my friend.  And that's the power you have", "docId": "the-insider_shooting.txt", "asentId": 25, "question": "I believe that?  Yes, I believe that", "qsentId": 24}, {"answer": "Well, we'd certainly be interested in making his acquaintance, but without knowing what he's going to do..", "docId": "the-insider_shooting.txt", "asentId": 27, "question": " It would be better if he called us", "qsentId": 26}, {"answer": "Do you own a gun, Mr. my friend", "docId": "the-insider_shooting.txt", "asentId": 29, "question": "What caliber is your gun", "qsentId": 28}, {"answer": "A gun?  Yes", "docId": "the-insider_shooting.txt", "asentId": 31, "question": "What caliber is my gun", "qsentId": 30}, {"answer": "What caliber is your gun", "docId": "the-insider_shooting.txt", "asentId": 33, "question": "Yes, sir.  What caliber is your gun", "qsentId": 32}, {"answer": " ...taping?  What are you taping", "docId": "the-insider_shooting.txt", "asentId": 35, "question": " An interview!  Do you know what they will do to us...!  I thought...  Sorry", "qsentId": 34}, {"answer": "A delivery device for nicotine", "docId": "the-insider_shooting.txt", "asentId": 37, "question": "You're gonna get your fix..", "qsentId": 36}, {"answer": "What's changed", "docId": "the-insider_shooting.txt", "asentId": 39, "question": "No.  I mean since whenever..", "qsentId": 38}, {"answer": "There an echo in here?  Your objection's been recorded.  She typed it into her little machine over there.  It's on the record.  So now I'll proceed with my deposition of  witness.  Does it act as a drug", "docId": "the-insider_shooting.txt", "asentId": 41, "question": " Oh, you got rights  lefts!  Ups and downs and middles!  So what?!  You don't get to instruct  around here! This is not that place, not that place nor .  This is the sovereign State of 's proceeding.  Wipe that smirk off your face!  Dr. my friend's deposition  be part of this record.  And I'm going to take my witness' testimony!  Whether the hell you like it or not!  Answer the question, Dr..", "qsentId": 40}, {"answer": " my friend, how are you?  How's the family, okay", "docId": "the-insider_shooting.txt", "asentId": 43, "question": " What do you mean there is no family", "qsentId": 42}, {"answer": "B", "docId": "the-insider_shooting.txt", "asentId": 45, "question": "No?  No, what", "qsentId": 44}, {"answer": "Well, what do you think I'm going to do? Quit in protest?  I'm not going to do that", "docId": "the-insider_shooting.txt", "asentId": 47, "question": "No.  I'm  going to take", "qsentId": 46}, {"answer": " You're taking", "docId": "the-insider_shooting.txt", "asentId": 49, "question": "Then what  you going to do", "qsentId": 48}, {"answer": "To make it even a little more attractive, I don't know if you're ever gonna get paid", "docId": "the-insider_shooting.txt", "asentId": 51, "question": "That's a good question. ", "qsentId": 50}, {"answer": "Time?  Bullshit!  You corporate lackey! Who told you your incompetent little fingers had the requisite skills to edit me!  I'm trying to Ban", "docId": "the-insider_shooting.txt", "asentId": 53, "question": "\"my friend", "qsentId": 52}, {"answer": "Free press?  Press is free...for anyone who owns one.  my friend has a free press", "docId": "the-insider_shooting.txt", "asentId": 55, "question": "I got perspective", "qsentId": 54}, {"answer": "No, you do not", "docId": "the-insider_shooting.txt", "asentId": 57, "question": "You're not listening.  Really know what you're going to do before you do it", "qsentId": 56}, {"answer": "How prominent?  What kind of placement", "docId": "the-insider_shooting.txt", "asentId": 59, "question": "Well, until you do, all I can tell you is what you already know...they will not air an interview", "qsentId": 58}]